pickmanager.com 2009-09-04

# PickManager.com - 2009 Fantasy Football - Play All You Want, Win All You Can

**Introduction.**   
We take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel comfortable using our web site. This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information (referred to as "Data" below) that may be collected by us on our site. This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control. 

**1\. Collection and Use of Data.**   
This Web Site collects certain information relative to users who visit the site. Our registration process requires only a valid e-mail address and a unique user ID and password. Providing us with other information is at your option. Please take note that your user name, e-mail address, or other submissions that you make on this site may contain your real name or other personally identifiable information and, as a result, may appear on this site. Like many web sites, we may also automatically receive general information that is contained in our server log files such as your IP address and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if at all) is set forth below.

This Web site categorizes this information into certain categories and the privacy level and what we do with the information that we collect on you depends upon the category in which you fall. 

Our company does not make any attempt to obtain information that personally identifies our users who visit our web site. It is not our policy to sell or otherwise provide access to such information to unaffiliated third parties.

_Category I_ – Information on users who visit our site to read or download information on our pages. From these users, we collect and store only the following information: 

   1\. The domain name through which you gained access to our Web site;  
   2\. The precise time and date that you entered our web site.  
   3\. The URL of the web page through which you kinked to our web site.

_Category II_ – Users who send us e-mail containing personal information or identifies you, sign our guest book, or request email publications. Any information that we collect in this way is used only for purposes of responding to you and addressing the issues that you may have raised.

Any information that we collect is collected as part of our business practices in order to identify demographic information relative to users who access our site, assessing the number and type of user accessing various sections of our site, helping us determine what content and business concepts are working for us and/or are of interest to our visitors, determining technical design features and specifications and helping us assess systems performance. We also use such information in statistical form to assist us in business and marketing strategies and programs. We utilize software programs to create summary statistics which we utilize for the above purposes.

As a security measure for ourselves and our users, we utilize certain software programs to monitor traffic to our site and within our network. This software also enables us to identify unauthorized upload attempts, access to our system, and other attempts to cause damage to our systems.

We may use Data to customize and improve your user experience on this site. We will make efforts so that your Data **_will not be_** provided to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) we obtain your consent, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires the interaction with or is provided by a third party, by way of example an Application Service Provider; (iv) pursuant to legal process or law enforcement; (v) we find that your use of this site violates our this Policy, Terms of Service, other usage guidelines or as deemed reasonably necessary by us to protect our legal rights and/or property; (vi) or this site is purchased by a third party whereby that third party will be able to use the Data in the same manner as we can as set forth in this Policy. In the event you choose to use links that appear on our site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites.

**3\. Cookies.**   
Like many web sites, we set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings. Advertisements may appear on our web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the advertisement. However, the companies serving the advertising do not have access to our cookies. These companies usually use non-personally identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to our site. You can contact the advertising companies to find out more information about this practice and to find out about your options including from the following companies that may serve advertising on our site.

**4\. Children.**   
We do not allow persons under the age of 18 to become members of this site. We do not collect information from any person under the age of 13 and we will reject and delete any attempted registration by any person believed in good faith to be under the age of 13. Furthermore, any false or fraudulent entry or registration from a person under the age of 13 will be deemed ineligible. We are in full compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA Act). For more information, please contact our Webmaster through the contact section of the web site.

**5\. Editing or Deleting Your Account Information.**   
We provide you with the ability to edit the information in your user account information that you provided to us in registration at your member home page. You may request deletion of your user account by contacting our Webmaster through the contact section of the web site.

Content or other data that you may have provided to us and that is not contained within your user account, such as posts that may appear within our forums, may continue to remain on our site at our discretion even though your user account is deleted. 

**6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy.**   
We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message to the e-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings.

**7\. NO GUARANTEES.**   
While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of Data and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of Data.

**8\. Contact Information.**   
If you have any questions about this Policy or our web site, please feel free to contact our Webmaster through the contact section of the web site.
